Guide to the Francis J. McNamara papers, 1928-1997
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 1: Anti-Communism and Subversive Activities, 1928-1975; (154 boxes)
  - FBI-Arlington apartment bust-in, 1975-1978 (Folder 9, Box 46)
    Hearst, Patricia, United States Court of Appeals
  - FBI - Boggs-Reuss Dowdy-Gallagher, 1971-1984 (Folder 1, Box 47)
    Congressional Record, FBI, Hoover
  - FBI-books, films, TV, etc., 1975-1979 (Folder 2, Box 47)
    Face the Nation, Fiction, Media
  - FBI building, 1971-1979 (Folder 3, Box 47)
    History of the FBI
  - FBI-CIA Book, 1971-1980 (Folder 4, Box 47)
    Customs, FDR, Mail Opening, United States v. Ramsey,
  - FBI, CIA - Undermine, 1950-1978 (Folder 5, Box 47)
    Communist Threat, Congressional Record, War on FBI
  - FBI, CIA - Undermine, 1950-1978 (Folder 6, Box 47)
    Anti-Communism, Communist Foreigners, The Nation
  - FBI-corruption and convictions (crime), 1973-1980 (Folder 7, Box 47)
    Corruption, Misconduct in FBI, Oversight
  - FBI-Gray, L. Patrick (Folder 8, Box 47)
    Nixon, Gray
  - FBI-Hill files, 1971-1975 (Folder 9, Box 47)
    About FBI Files on Senators and Congressmen
  - FBI-House Intelligence Committee, 1975-1976 (Folder 10, Box 47)
    FBI Probe, Intelligence
  - FBI-Kennedy assassination, 1975-1977 (Folder 11, Box 47)
    Assassinations, Lee Harvey Oswald, Jack Ruby
  - FBI - miscellaneous Far East policy (Folder 12, Box 47)
    CBS, FBI, McCarthy
  - FBI-Senate Intelligence Committee, 1975-1976 (Folder 13, Box 47)
    Domestic Spying, Political Abuse, Senate Intelligence Committee
  - FBI-domestic intelligence, 1974-1993 (Folder 14, Box 47)
    FBI, Intelligence
  - FBI and drug enforcement, 1950-1982 (Folder 1, Box 48)
    Drugs, FBI
  - FBI-FCI, 1975-1987 (Folder 2, Box 48)
    Counter Intelligence
  - FBI guidelines FCI, 1975-1984 (Folder 3, Box 48)
  - FBI-[Clarence M.] Kelly, 1973-1978 (Folder 4, Box 48)
    FBI, Kelley
  - FBI-[Clarence M.] Kelly, 1973-1978 (Folder 5, Box 48)
  - FBI-media, PA, 1971-1978 (Folder 6, Box 48)
    FBI, Inside Washington
  - FBI-Martin Luther King, 1964-1978 (Folder 7, Box 48)
    Assassinations, Congressional Record, FBI
  - FBI-oversight, 1971-1975 (Folder 8, Box 48)
    Espionage, Oversight
  - FBI-personnel (officials), 1974-1986 (Folder 9, Box 48)
    FBI, Retirements
  - FBI punishments, 1975-1980 (Folder 10, Box 48)
    FBI, Firings
  - FBI-sour agents and informants, 1971-1981 (Folder 11, Box 48)
    FBI, Intelligence Leaks
  - Federal Employee Security Program, 1970-1971 (Folder 1, Box 49)
    Federal Jobs, Protests
  - Feinberg law, 1950 (Folder 2, Box 49)
    Anti-Communism, Court of Appeals, Supreme Court
  - FFR-CSD 1, 1958-1966 (Folder 3, Box 49)
    Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, Fund for the Republic
  - FFR-CSD 1, 1958-1966 (Folder 4, Box 49)
  - FFR-CSD 1 Robert Hutchins, 1955-1956 (Folder 5, Box 49)
  - FGS, 1960-1965 (Folder 6, Box 49)
    Anti-Communism, Communist Party, McCarthy
  - Fielding break-in NV and theft of Ellesberg papers, 1960-1978 (Folder 7, Box 49)
    Cleveland State Law Review, Ellsberg, Daniel
  - Fifth Amendment, 1953-1978 (Folder 8, Box 49)
    Constitutional Privelege, Federal Employment, Fifth Amendment Problems
  - Fifth Amendment, 1954-1977 (Folder 9, Box 49)
    The Fifth Amendment Today
  - Fifth Amendment, 1954-1977 (Folder 1, Box 50)
    Congressional Records, Fifth Amendment Problems
  - Fifth Avenue Peace Parade Committee, 1973 (Folder 2, Box 50)
    Fifth Avenue Peace Parade Committee v. L. Patrick Gray
  - Film-general [Hollywood], 1951-1988 (Folder 3, Box 50)
    Communism, Film, Hollywood
  - Film-general [Hollywood], 1951-1988 (Folder 4, Box 50)
    Communism, Film, Hollywood, HUAC
  - Film-general: Hollywood, 1951-1988 (Folder 5, Box 50)
    Congress, Hollywood
  - Film-stage-etc., 1950-1995 (Folder 6, Box 50)
    Actors, All-American Conference, Communism, McNamara
  - First Amendment, 1951-1995 (Folder 7, Box 50)
    Courts, Newspaper Clippings
  - First Principles: first two volumes, 1975-1977 (Folder 8, Box 50)
    Civil Liberties, First Principles, National Security
  - First Principles: first two volumes, 1975-1977 (Folder 9, Box 50)
  - FOIA amendments, 1974 (Folder 10, Box 50)
    Freedom of Information Act
  - FOIA-NSA etc., 1969-1981 (Folder 1, Box 51)
    Freedom of Information Act, National Security Agency
  - FOIA-security (nuclear etc.), 1974-1982 (Folder 2, Box 51)
    Freedom of Information Act, National Security, Nuclear Weapons
  - FOIA-subversive use, 1973-1982 (Folder 3, Box 51)
    Freedom of Information Act, Subversive Activity
  - FOIA - US Supreme Court, 1972-1982 (Folder 4, Box 51)
    Supreme Court, Freedom of Information Act
  - Fonda, Jane, 1971-1985 (Folder 5, Box 51)
    Fonda, Jane, Hollywood, Newspaper Clippings
  - Fonda, Jane, 1972-1992 (Folder 6, Box 51)
  - Ford, Gerald - assassination attempt, 1975-1985 (Folder 7, Box 51)
    Fromme, Moore, Good, Manson
  - Foreign Attacks, 1969-1982 (Folder 8, Box 51)
    Claims by Foreign Governments Against the CIA
  - Unity- Foreign Intelligence- Domestic Intelligence, 1971-1979 (Folder 9, Box 51)
    Congressional Records, CIA, FBI, Intelligence
  - Foreign intelligence court, 1967-1983 (Folder 10, Box 51)
    Inside Washington, Intelligence, Newspaper Clippings
  - Foreign intelligence organizations, 1973-1985 (Folder 11, Box 51)
    Britain, Israel, KGB, Newspaper Clippings, Secret Agents, Yugoslavia
  - Foreign intelligence organizations, 1973-1985 (Folder 12, Box 51)
    Britain, Iran, KGB, Newspaper Clippings, Terrorism, Yugoslavia
  - Foreign Policy Pamphlets, 1939-1961 (Folder 1, Box 52)
    Foreign Policy, Nonfiction
  - Foreign terrorists in U.S., 1973-1981 (Folder 2, Box 52)
    Terrorism, National Security
  - Fort Dix, New Jersey, 1969 (Folder 3, Box 52)
    Military, Security
  - Fort Gordon-Fort Hood, 1969-1970 (Folder 4, Box 52)
  - Fort Monmouth, 1953-1956 (Folder 5, Box 52)
  - Foundation for American Research Incorporated, ca. 1945 (Folder 6, Box 52)
    Foundation for American Research, Pamphlet
  - Fourth Amendment, 1975-1994 (Folder 7, Box 52)
  - Fourth Amendment, 1975-1994 (Folder 8, Box 52)
    Newspaper Clippings, Surveillance
  - Fragging, 1971 (Folder 9, Box 52)
    Misuse of Grenades Outside of Combat
  - Frank Church - presidential campaign, 1975-1976 (Folder 10, Box 52)
    Church, Nixon, Reagan
  - Frank Church, 1971-1984 (Folder 11, Box 52)
    Church, KGB, Presidential Campaign, SALT II
  - Frank Church, 1971-1984 (Folder 12, Box 52)
    CIA Probe, Presidential Campaign
  - Freedom's facts against communism, 1954 - 1958 (Folder 1, Box 53)
    All-American Conference, Anti-Communism
  - Freedom's facts against communism, 1955 - 1956 (Folder 2, Box 53)
  - Freedom's facts against communism: publication of All American Conference, 1957 - 1958 (Folder 3, Box 53)
  - Freedom's facts against communism: publication of the All American Conference, 1959 (Folder 4, Box 53)
  - Freedom's facts against communism: publication of the All American Conference, 1960 (Folder 5, Box 53)
  - Freedom's facts against communism: publication of the All American Conference, 1961 - 1963 (Folder 6, Box 53)
  - Freedom's facts against communism, 1959 - 1969 (Folder 7, Box 53)
  - Freedom vs. Communism - Information and Action Materials, 1969 (Folder 8, Box 53)
    Action Kit, National Students Committee on Cold War Education
  - Free World Forum - vol. 3, no. 1., 1967 (Folder 1, Box 54)
    Journal on Foreign Affairs
  - Frontpage- Magazine of the Newspaper Guild of New York, Feb. 1948, April 1948 (Folder 2, Box 54)
    Magazine, Nonfiction
  - Fronts, 1945-1985 (Folder 3, Box 54)
    Anti-Communism, CPUSA Fronts, Newspaper Clippings
  - Fronts, 1969-1972 (Folder 4, Box 54)
    Anti-Communism, CPUSA Fronts, Subversive Activities Control Board
  - Fronts, 1949-1987 (Folder 5, Box 54)
    Anti-Communism, CPUSA Fronts
  - Fronts-forgeries, 1951-1990 (Folder 6, Box 54)
  - Fronts-forgeries, 1951-1990 (Folder 7, Box 54)
  - Senator Fulbright, J. William, 1958-1990 (Folder 8, Box 54)
    Congressional Records, Fullbright
  - Fund for Peace-[Stewart] Mott, 1973-1984 (Folder 9, Box 54)
    Nuclear Proliferation
  - General arts-GI's, 1969-1970 (Folder 1, Box 55)
    American Opinion, Armed Forces, War Protests
  - General-no use, 1969-1971 (Folder 2, Box 55)
    GI's Against Vietnam, Protest, Demonstration
  - General-useful, 1969-1971 (Folder 3, Box 55)
    Vietnam, Defense
  - General George Brown, 1974-1978 (Folder 4, Box 55)
    Congress, Newspaper Clippings
  - George Washington: Selections from His Writings, 1944 (Folder 5, Box 55)
    Washington, George
  - Germany (Baader, Meinhof), 1974-1994 (Folder 6, Box 55)
    German Leftist Terrorist Organizations and Activities, Hijacking
  - Germany (Baader, Meinhof), 1974-1994 (Folder 7, Box 55)
    German Leftist Terrorist Organizations and Activities
  - GI Civil Liberties Defense Committee, 1969 (Folder 8, Box 55)
    Anti-Vietnam War GI Organizations - GI Civil Libs. Defense Comm., GI Defense Org., Comm. for GI Rights, Patrick Def. Comm.
  - GI papers, 1969-1971 (Folder 9, Box 55)
    Newspapers, Nonfiction
  - GI papers, 1969-1971 (Folder 10, Box 55)
  - GI's United (Fort Jackson), 1969 (Folder 1, Box 56)
    Handouts, Young Socialist
  - Glomar Explorer, 1975-1978 (Folder 2, Box 56)
    CIA Ship, Deep Sea Mining Vessel
  - Goodman, Walter, 1968-1969 (Folder 3, Box 56)
    Articles, Memos, Receipts
  - GOP Convention, 1972 (Folder 4, Box 56)
    Political parties, Newspaper Clippings
  - Gould, Jack, 1950-1957 (Folder 5, Box 56)
    Letters, Newspaper Clippings
  - Government by Treason, 1946 (Folder 6, Box 56)
    Pamphlet, Snow, John Howland
  - Grasp the Weapon of Culture, 1951 (Folder 7, Box 56)
    Pamphlet, Jerome, V.J.
  - Senator Mike Gravel, 1971-1980 (Folder 8, Box 56)
    Newspaper Clippings, Gravel
  - Guilt by association, 1950-1953 (Folder 9, Box 56)
    Newspaper Clippings, United Auto Workers
  - Guyana, 1961-1976 (Folder 10, Box 56)
    Guyana, Soviet Union
  - Haldeman, Harry Robinson, 1970-1978 (Folder 11, Box 56)
    Haldeman, Newspaper Clippings
  - HALP - Press clips, Notes, etc. [folder 1 of 3], 1971-1993 (Folder 12, Box 56)
    Halperin
  - HALP - Press clips, Notes, etc. [folder 2 of 3], 1971-1976 (Folder 13, Box 56)
  - HALP - Press clips, Notes, etc. [folder 3 of 3], 1975-1993 (Folder 14, Box 56)
  - Halperin [Morton H.] and [Daniel] Ellsberg trial, 1972-1979 (Folder 1, Box 57)
  - Hammer, Armand, 1972-1987 (Folder 2, Box 57)
    Diplomacy, Hammer
  - Handschu v. Special Services [Division], 1972 (Folder 3, Box 57)
    Activists, Civil Rights Act, Lawsuit
  - Rep. Harrington [Michael], 1970s (Folder 4, Box 57)
    CIA, Chile, Congressional Hearing
  - Rep. Harrington [Michael], 1969-1976 (Folder 5, Box 57)
  - Hayden, Tom, 1970-1991 (Folder 6, Box 57)
    Jane Fonda, Hollywood
  - H-bomb/ A-bomb, 1950-1953 (Folder 7, Box 57)
    Defense, Nuclear Safety, Weapons Testing
  - Hearings before the Committee of Un-American Activities, House of Representatives, Eighty-First Congress, Second Session, March 24, 25 1950 (Folder 8, Box 57)
    Communist Party of Pennsylvania, HUAC
  - Hearings on Legislation to Outlaw Certain Un-American and Subversive Activities, 1950 (Folder 9, Box 57)
    HUAC, Subversive Activities
  - Hearst, Patricia, 1973-1994 (Folder 10, Box 57)
    Activists, Symbionese Liberation Army, SLA, Wanted Fugitives
  - Hearst, Patricia, 1973-1994 (Folder 11, Box 57)
  - Hearst, Patricia, 1974-1975 (Folder 1, Box 58)
  - Hearst, Patricia, 1974-1975 (Folder 2, Box 58)
  - Hellman, Lillian, 1969-1993 (Folder 3, Box 58)
    Communist Sympathizers, Newspaper Clippings, Playwrights
  - Hellman, Lillian, 1969-1993 (Folder 4, Box 58)
  - Helms, Richard, 1973-1993 (Folder 5, Box 58)
    CIA, Committee on Foreign Relations, Congress, Security, Watergate
  - Helms, Richard, 1973-1993 (Folder 6, Box 58)
    CIA, Committee on Foreign Relations, Congress, Iran, Security, Watergate
  - Helms, Richard, 1973-1993 (Folder 7, Box 58)
    CIA, Committee on Foreign Relations, Congress, Iran, Security
  - Helms, Richard - Congress communications, 1976-1977 (Folder 1, Box 59)
  - Helms [Richard]-Congress comm[unications], 1980 (Folder 2, Box 59)
  - Herblock - Alan Barth, 1951-1957 (Folder 3, Box 59)
    Political Cartoons
  - Hersh, Seymour, 1969-1983 (Folder 4, Box 59)
    Investigations, Journalism, Mai Lai
  - Hijacking - legislation and measures against, 1974-1977 (Folder 5, Box 59)
    Hijacking, Newspaper Clippings
  - Hijack INQ-plane, 1972-1984 (Folder 6, Box 59)
  - HISC, 1970-1977 (Folder 7, Box 59)
    House Internal Security Committee
  - HISC, 1970-1977 (Folder 8, Box 59)
  - HISC, 1973-1975 (Folder 9, Box 59)
  - HISC-end and judicial, 1974-1979 (Folder 10, Box 59)
  - HISC-Revive, 1975-1981 (Folder 11, Box 59)
  - HISC minority, ca. 1970 (Folder 12, Box 59)
  - HCUA-HISC Replies to critics and plugs, 1964-1974 (Folder 1, Box 60)
  - HISC-HUAC-SISS-terror, 1972-1977 (Folder 2, Box 60)
    House Internal Security Committee, House Un-American Activities Committee
  - HUAC-HISC-new name and mandate-rules of procedure, 1969 (Folder 3, Box 60)
  - Hiss, Alger Horsky, 1949-1980 (Folder 4, Box 60)
    Espionage, State Department, Soviet Spy, United Nations
  - Hiss, Alger Horsky, 1959-1986 (Folder 5, Box 60)
  - Hiss, Alger Horsky, 1950-1992 (Folder 6, Box 60)
  - Hobbson, Julius, 1970-1982 (Folder 7, Box 60)
    D.C. Statehood Party, Newspaper Clippings
  - Hoffman, Abbie, 1970-1989 (Folder 8, Box 60)
    Communism, Fugitives, Youth International Party, YIP
  - Hoffman, Paul - to insure hysterical end, 1950-1957 (Folder 9, Box 60)
    CIA, Soviet Union, United Nations
  - Hollywood - Aware, 1953-1975 (Folder 10, Box 60)
    Communism, Hollywood
  - Hollywood - Aware, 1954-1957 (Folder 11, Box 60)
  - Hollywood-$BCP, 1951-1966 (Folder 12, Box 60)
    Film, Hollywood
  - Hollywood - Bessie, Alvah, 1975-1985 (Folder 1, Box 61)
    Hollywood
  - Hollywood - Biberman, Sondergaard, Herbert and Edward, 1951-1970 (Folder 2, Box 61)
  - Hollywood "blacklist"-screening, 1951-1962 (Folder 3, Box 61)
  - Hollywood - Cole, Lester, 1951-1966 (Folder 4, Box 61)
  - Hollywood and CP, 1951-1983 (Folder 5, Box 61)
    Communist Party, Hollywood
  - Hollywood - CP Art Doctrine-Film, 1946-1963 (Folder 6, Box 61)
  - Hollywood - Dmytryk, Ed, 1951 (Folder 7, Box 61)
  - Hollywood - Entertainment, 1952-1958 (Folder 8, Box 61)
  - Hollywood - Entertainment, 1951-1993 (Folder 9, Box 61)
  - Hollywood - Entertainment, 1949-1994 (Folder 10, Box 61)
  - Hollywood - Faulk, John Henry-"Fear On Trial" (CBS), 1956-1983 (Folder 11, Box 61)
  - Hollywood - film content, 1949-1971 (Folder 12, Box 61)
  - Hollywood - Gray, Barry, 1942-1955 (Folder 13, Box 61)
  - Hollywood - Jarrico, Paul-Wilner, Sylvia-Tiba, Geo, 1951 (Folder 14, Box 61)
  - Hollywood - JFK-Stone-Costner, 1991-1992 (Folder 1, Box 62)
    Costner, Kevin, Film, Kennedy, John F.
  - Hollywood - Larder, Ring Jr., 1961-1985 (Folder 2, Box 62)
  - Hollywood - Lawson, John Howard, 1951-1977 (Folder 3, Box 62)
  - Hollywood - Lear P.A.W.--Mash, 1975-1988 (Folder 4, Box 62)
    Hollywood, Lear, Norman, TV
  - Hollywood - Maltz and Sinatra, 1951-1965 (Folder 5, Box 62)
    Sinatra, Frank, Music, Hollywood
  - Hollywood - McCrary, Tex and Falkenburg, Jiny, 1950-1952 (Folder 6, Box 62)
  - Hollywood - Miller, Merle, 1950-1962 (Folder 7, Box 62)
  - Hollywood - MPA (Motion Picture Alliance), 1951-1985 (Folder 8, Box 62)
    Hollywood, Movies
  - Hollywood - Ornitz, Sam, 1947 (Folder 9, Box 62)
  - Hollywood - Party-line films, 1955-1960 (Folder 10, Box 62)
  - Hollywood - Polonsky [Abraham], 1951-1970 (Folder 11, Box 62)
  - Hollywood - Radio writers guild-"We the undersigned", 1952 (Folder 12, Box 62)
    Hollywood, Radio
  - Hollywood - "Reds", 1981-1985 (Folder 13, Box 62)
  - Hollywood - Scott, Robert Adrian, 1972 (Folder 14, Box 62)
  - Hollywood - Taylor, Robert, 1990 (Folder 15, Box 62)
  - Hollywood ten, 1951-1970 (Folder 16, Box 62)
  - Hollywood - Trumbo, Dalton, 1961-1978 (Folder 17, Box 62)
  - Hollywood - Wilson, Michael, 1951-1978 (Folder 18, Box 62)
  - Hollywood hearing, 1951 (Folder 1, Box 63)
  - Hollywood hearing, 1951 (Folder 2, Box 63)
  - Hollywood - Music - Blacklisting, 1954-1990 (Folder 3, Box 63)
    Music, Hollywood, Communism
  - Hollywood - Music - Blacklisting, 1954-1990 (Folder 4, Box 63)
  - Hollywood - Music - Blacklisting, 1954-1990 (Folder 5, Box 63)
  - Hollywood - Music - Blacklisting, 1954-1990 (Folder 6, Box 63)
  - Hollywood - Music - Blacklisting, 1954-1992 (Folder 7, Box 63)
  - Hollywood - Music - Blacklisting, 1954-1992 (Folder 1, Box 64)
  - Hollywood - Music - Blacklisting, 1954-1992 (Folder 2, Box 64)
  - Homosexuality and security, 1973-1995 (Folder 3, Box 64)
    Security
  - Homosexuality and security, 1973-1995 (Folder 4, Box 64)
  - Hoover Doctrine, 1950-1959 (Folder 5, Box 64)
    Hoover, J. Edgar, FBI
  - Horsky, Charles A.-Alger Hiss, 1945-1964 (Folder 6, Box 64)
    Espionage, State Department
  - House Committee on Un-American Activities, 1958-1963 (Folder 7, Box 64)
    HUAC
  - Housing - State, 1950s (Folder 8, Box 64)
    Housing Projects and Communism
  - House Left, 1968-1980 (Folder 9, Box 64)
    Congress, Liberalism
  - Houston, 1975-1991 (Folder 1, Box 65)
    Police Department, Security
  - H.R. 9669, 1970-1973 (Folder 2, Box 65)
    Congressional Record, Molly Kwauk
  - H.R. 9669, 1970-1973 (Folder 3, Box 65)
  - HUAC - Communist Methods of Infiltration, 1953 (Folder 4, Box 65)
    House Un-American Activities Committee
  - HUAC - Investigation of communist activities in the San Francisco area, 1953 (Folder 5, Box 65)
  - HUAC - Investigation of Communist Activities in the Los Angeles Area, 1953 (Folder 6, Box 65)
  - HUAC - Organized Communism in the United States, August 19, 1953 (Folder 7, Box 65)
  - HUAC - Investigation of Communist Activities New York Area - Part 1 - (Testimony of Jean Muir), June 15, 1953 (Folder 8, Box 65)
  - HUAC - Investigation of Un-American Propaganda Activities in the United States, December 15, 1938 (Folder 9, Box 65)
  - HUAC - Hearings Regarding Communist Activities Among Farm Groups, February 28, March 9 1951 (Folder 10, Box 65)
  - HUAC - Reports on the Communist "Peace" Offensive, April 1, 1951 (Folder 11, Box 65)
  - HUAC - Hearings Relating to Communist Activities in the Defense Area of Baltimore, 1951 (Folder 12, Box 65)
  - HUAC - Hearings on American Aspects of the Richard Sorge Spy Case, August 9, 22, 23 1951 (Folder 13, Box 65)
  - HUAC - Testimony of Oliver Edmund Clubb, March 14, August 20, 23 1951 (Folder 14, Box 65)
  - HUAC - Statements on the March of Treason, February 19, 1951 (Folder 15, Box 65)
  - HUAC - 100 Things You Should Know About Communism, May 14, 1951 (Folder 1, Box 66)
  - HUAC - Communist Tactics Among Veteran's Groups (Testimony of John T. Pace), 1951 (Folder 2, Box 66)
  - HUAC - Expose of Communist Activities in the State of Massachusetts, 1951 (Folder 3, Box 66)
  - HUAC - Hearings Regarding Communist Activities in the Territory of Hawaii - Part 4, 1951 (Folder 4, Box 66)
  - HUAC - Guide to Subversive Organizations and Publications (and appendix), 1951 (Folder 5, Box 66)
  - HUAC - The Shameful Years, December 30, 1951 (Folder 6, Box 66)
  - HUAC - Second Report: Un-American Activities in California, 1945 (Folder 7, Box 66)
  - HUAC - Fourth Report: Un-American Activities in California - Communist Front Organizations, 1948 (Folder 8, Box 66)
  - HUAC - Fifth Report: Un-American Activities in California, 1949 (Folder 9, Box 66)
  - HUAC - Sixth Report: Un-American Activities in California, 1951 (Folder 10, Box 66)
  - HUAC - Seventh Report: Un-American Activities in California, 1953 (Folder 11, Box 66)
  - HUAC - Eighth Report: Un-American Activities in California, 1955 (Folder 1, Box 67)
  - HUAC - Ninth Report: Un-American Activities in California, 1957 (Folder 2, Box 67)
  - HUAC - Tenth Report: Un-American Activities in California, 1959 (Folder 3, Box 67)
  - HUAC - Eleventh Report: Un-American Activities in California, 1961 (Folder 4, Box 67)
  - HUAC - Twelfth Report: Un-American Activities in California, 1963 (Folder 5, Box 67)
  - HUAC - Thirteenth: Un-American Activities in California, 1965 (Folder 6, Box 67)
  - HUAC - Thirteenth Report Supplement on Un-American Activities in California, 1966 (Folder 7, Box 67)
  - HUAC - Fourteenth Report: Un-American Activities in California, 1967 (Folder 8, Box 67)
  - HUAC - Fifteenth Report: Un-American Activities in California, 1970 (Folder 9, Box 67)
  - HUAC - Index: Un-American Activities in California.`, 1943, 1945, 1947, 1949, 1951 (Folder 1, Box 68)
  - HUAC - Index: Un-American Activities in California, 1943, 1945, 1947, 1949, 1951, 1953, 1955, 1957, 1959, 1961, 1963. (Folder 2, Box 68)
  - HUAC - Report of the Un-American Activities Commission - State of Ohio., 1953-1954 (Folder 3, Box 68)
  - HUAC - Report on Investigation of Subversive Activities In Florida, 1955 (Folder 4, Box 68)
  - HUAC - Subversive Activities in New Hampshire, 1955 (Folder 5, Box 68)
  - HUAC - A Report to the 1962 Regular Session Mississippi State Legislature (Folder 6, Box 68)
  - HUAC Staff Memos, 1950s (Folder 7, Box 68)
  - HUAC - Legal Soviet "Espionage" MCN, 1951-1969 (Folder 8, Box 68)
  - HUAC - "Preliminary Report on Neo-Fascist and Hate-Groups" December 17, 1954 (Folder 9, Box 68)
  - HUAC - "Colonization of America's Basic Industries by the Communist Party of the U.S.A.", September 3, 1954 (Folder 1, Box 69)
  - HUAC - "The American Negro in the Communist Party", December 22, 1954 (Folder 2, Box 69)
  - HUAC - "Report on the March of Labor", December 22, 1954 (Folder 3, Box 69)
  - HUAC - "This if Your House Committee on Un-American Activities", September 19, 1954 (Folder 4, Box 69)
  - HUAC - "Investigation of Communist Activities in the State of Florida" - Hearings - Part 1, November 29, 30, 1954 - (Folder 5, Box 69)
  - HUAC - "Investigation of Communist Activities in the State of Florida" - Hearings - Part 2, December 1, 1954. (Folder 6, Box 69)
  - HUAC - "Communist Methods of Infiltration" (Entertainment, Part 2) - Hearing, December 14, 1954 (Folder 7, Box 69)
  - HUAC - "Investigation of Communist Activities in the Dayton, Ohio area" - Hearing - Part 1, September 13 - 15, 1954 (Folder 8, Box 69)
  - HUAC - "Investigation of Communist Activities in the Dayton, Ohio area" - Hearings - Part 2, September 14, 1954 (Folder 9, Box 69)
  - HUAC - "Investigation of Communist Activities in the Dayton, Ohio area" - Hearings - Part 3, September 15, 1954 (Folder 10, Box 69)
  - HUAC - "Investigation of Communist Activities in the Dayton, Ohio area" - Hearings - Part 4, November 17, 1954 (Folder 11, Box 69)
  - HUAC - "Communist Methods of Infiltration" (government - labor, part 4) - Hearings - [2 copies], January 13, December 15, 1954 (Folder 12, Box 69)
  - HUAC - "Investigation of Communist Activities in the Philadelphia Area" - Hearings - Part 5, July 30, 1954 (Folder 13, Box 69)
  - HUAC - "Communist Methods of Infiltration" (Education - part 8) - Hearings, April 21, June 8, 1953, April 12, 1954 (Folder 14, Box 69)
  - HUAC - "Communist Methods of Infiltration" (Education - part 9) - Hearings, June 28, 29 1954 (Folder 15, Box 69)
  - HUAC - "Investigation of Communist Activities in the State of California" - Hearings - Part 11, September 17, 1954 (Folder 16, Box 69)
  - HUAC - "Investigation of Communist Activities in the State of Michigan" - Hearings - Part 11, November 17, 1954 (Folder 17, Box 69)
  - HUAC - "Investigation of Communist Activities in the State of Michigan" - Hearings - Part 12, November 18, 19 1954 (Folder 18, Box 69)
  - HUAC - "Conference on Cold War Education", 1963 (Folder 19, Box 69)
  - HUAC - "World Anti-Communist Congress" Stationary and Letter, 1958 (Folder 20, Box 69)